<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>roddyrap.advancedmedicinepolicies</packageId>
	<name>Advanced Medicine Policies</name>
	<author>Roddy Rappaport</author>
	<url>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3701592043</url>
	<modVersion>0.1.1</modVersion>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.6</li>
	</supportedVersions>

	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>

	<incompatibleWith>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</incompatibleWith>

	<loadBefore>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</loadBefore>
	
	<loadAfter>
		<!-- <li>username.modname</li> -->
	</loadAfter>

	<description>Have you ever ran out of medicine becuase your doctor wasted all of it on cosmetics?
Did one of your pawns ever die because you resticted them to herbal medicine long ago and forgot to change it?

No longer!

This mod adds additional medicine policies that will allow you to always use the correct medicine
automatically (After you configure the rules). You will not need to manually change the preffered
medicine for a pawn each time anymore.

This mod allows you to choose different preffered medicines based on combinations from two categories:
- Pawn Allegiance: You can choose policies for colonists, prisoners, slaves, animals and more differently.
- Pawn Conditions: You can choose policies for surgeris, life-threatening injuries, bleeding out, immunity disease, chronic disease, bruises-only, self-tend.

Combine these values to create rules. Rules are always matched from the first (top) one to the
bottom one. Order matters!

NOTE: The allegiance selector for non-colonist pawns/animals is not guaranteed to work properly and may clash with the default medicine preferences for the relevant categories.

The self-tend icon is used with permission from Jaxe's highly recommended RimHUD mod.

Source Code: https://github.com/roddyrap/rimworld-advanced-medicine-policies</description>
</ModMetaData>